CHRISTOPHER KSIAZAK

PROJECT COORDINATOR

Summary

Hello! I'm Chris, a developer born and raised in El Paso, TX. I enjoy learning new technologies and applying that knowledge in designing and creating web applications.

Currently, I serve as a Project Coordinator at C3i Solutions, I'd say I'm about 95% autonomous as I collaborate with our client across various time zones. Before this, I attended the University of Texas at El Paso (UTEP). I realized that Electrical Engineering wasn't a topic that I quite enjoyed, so I joined the Full Stack Web Development program at Lambda School, which has provided me valuable experience in application development with distributed teams.

Employment

C3i Solutions Project Coordinator

El Paso, TX Mar. 2017 to Current

I joined C3i solutions in March of 2017, starting off as a support representative for our client Castlight Health. I was promptly promoted to Project Coordinator. From there, I assisted in developing our program from a support oriented role into a technical one. As we transitioned through several product launches, I assisted in knowledge base development, processing reporting checks via Salesforce and JIRA, and quantified that data to determine trends. At the moment, I assist in maintaining the client's relationship with Anthem by overseeing support incidents, analyzing flat files, and validating API requests.

Best Buy Samsung Sales Associate

El Paso, Texas June 2014 to Mar. 2015

At Best Buy, I strove to meet sales goals by listening to the customer's needs, wants, and desires, then using that information, I was able to provide a total solution based on my product knowledge. I was promoted from a regular home theater consultant to a Samsung representative. This granted me the opportunity to provide Samsung specific training and ensuring our premium displays were organized and up to date. I departed to focus on school full time.

Sears Sales Consultant

El Paso, Texas Aug. 2013 to Apr. 2014

At Sears, I regularly met sales and customer experience goals within the mattress department. Once again, this was achieved by asking open ended questions to better understand the customer's problems. I would pair them up with a product that would suit those needs, which in turn not only made the customer happy, but also reduced returns and exchanges.

Before leaving, I was able to lead the department's product refresh.

Projects

Ksiazak.dev

Ksiazak.dev is my personal portfolio page. Version 2.0 is built using Gatsby, has full SEO, and is completely responsive. Stylized with JSS. Currently, the data is hard-coded, but in the future, I plan on connecting a headless CMS and querying it using GraphQL.

Optimal Airbnb Pricing API

For this project, I was the sole back end developer. Here, I created as server using Node, then used Knex (SQL query builder) to migrate and seed the database, and a combination of Heroku and PostgreSQL to host the server and database. It features JWT authentication and bcrypt for hashing passwords. I worked with both the Front End and Data Science teams to ensure the data is processed and parsed without issue. As I am experienced in React, I also assisted the front end team in debugging any issues with their application.

SongSight

SongSight allows you to select from a list of songs, save that song, or return similar songs based on dance-ability, key, and other metrics. Here, I served as the Front End Architect and lead group discussions on planning the application layout and features. I worked with 3 other Front End Developers, our Back End Team, and the Data Science in completing this project. I used React, Router, and Redux.

Contact

- cksiazak@gmail.com
- ksiazak.dev
- **(915) 253-8705**
- **♥** El Paso, Texas
- **y** cksiazak_dev
- in cksiazak
- C) cksiazak

Education

Lambda School

Apr. 2019 to Current

Skills

WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML5

CSS (LESS/SASS)

Javascript

React

Redux

Node

SQL Gatsby

Nextis

PostgreSOL

REPORTING, DOCUMENTATION, AND ANALYTICS

JIRA

Tableau

Confluence

Datadog

Salesforce

ExactTarget